(Howard:)I wonder if only a baby
who is worthy
(Howard:)can suckle at the bosom of Thor.
PENNY:
Okay, new salon topic.
(Penny:)Salons-- dumb thing
from a long time ago
(Penny:)or interesting thing made dumb
by talking about superheroes?
(Penny:)Discuss.
(Sheldon:)I don't believe it matters
what the topic is.
(Sheldon:)What's crucial for a salon
(Sheldon:)is that we conduct
the discussion
(Sheldon:)in an elevated
and insightful way.
(Sheldon:)It's all about the execution.
(Leonard:)Of course you'd focus on that
rather than the inspiration.
(Leonard:)Uh, new salon topic.
(Leonard:)What's more important,
an idea or its execution?
Oh, that's fun.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, good for you, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)That's a lovely little notion.
(Sheldon:)Kind of like,
"I wish I could talk
to my uncle in Chicago."
(Sheldon:)Yeah, now stand back
while I invent the telephone.
"Hello? Oh, hold on."
(Sheldon:)Leonard, it's your uncle.
(Sheldon:)He says you just got burned.
(Amy:)Sheldon.
(Stuart:)You guys.
No, it's okay.
(Leonard:)We're all adults trying to have
an intelligent discussion.
(Leonard:)At least I am.
(Leonard:)Howard, what
do you think?
(Howard:)Well, I guess, as an engineer,
I lean towards execution.